The next thing we are going to do now that we have primed her skin with a foundation primer is we are going to apply some liquid foundation.
This is a really nice, light weight, oil free, liquid foundation.
One thing you want to be sure of when you are choosing a foundation for yourself is you want to make sure it blends really well into the skin.
If you put a stripe on the side of the face from cheek to jaw it should blend in perfectly.
It should not leave any noticeable mark of demarcation along the jaw because you should never be able to see where your face ends and your neck begins.
It should just blend in really perfectly.
This color is a really good match for her skin.
We are going to take a little bit of this.
I am going to use my foundation brush and we are just going to brush this all over just to even out her complexion and give her a little bit of light coverage.
The nice thing about this particular foundation is that it is a buildable coverage so you can use a layering affect with it if you need to and it won't look heavy or cakey.